(light upbeat music)
♪ Day to night to morning,
keep with me in the moment ♪
♪ I'd let you had I known
it, why don't you say so ♪
♪ Didn't even notice, no
punches left to roll with ♪
♪ You got to keep me focused,
you want it, say so ♪
♪ Day to night to morning,
keep with me in the moment ♪
♪ I'd let you had I known
it, why don't you say so ♪
♪ Didn't even notice, no
punches left to roll with ♪
♪ You got to keep me focused,
you want it, say so ♪
♪ It's been a long time
since you fell in love ♪
♪ You ain't coming out your shell ♪
♪ You really ain't been yourself ♪
♪ Tell me what must I
do, do tell, my love ♪
♪ 'Cause luckily I'm good at reading ♪
♪ I wouldn't bug him, but
he won't stop cheesin' ♪
♪ And we can dance all day around it ♪
♪ If you front then I'll be bouncing ♪
♪ If you want it scream
and shout it, babe ♪
♪ Before I leave you dry ♪
♪ Day to night to morning,
keep with me in the moment ♪
♪ I'd let you had I known
it, why don't you say so ♪
♪ Didn't even notice, no
punches left to roll with ♪
♪ You got to keep me focused,
you want it, say so ♪
♪ Day to night to morning,
keep with me in the moment ♪
♪ I'd let you had I known
it, why don't you say so ♪
♪ Didn't even notice, no
punches left to roll with ♪
♪ You got to keep me focused,
you want it, say so ♪
♪ Let me check my chest,
my breath right quick ♪
♪ He ain't never seen it
in a dress like this ♪
♪ He ain't never even
been impressed like this ♪
♪ Prolly why I got him
quiet on the set like zip ♪
♪ Like it, love it, need it bad ♪
♪ Take it, own it, steal it, fast ♪
♪ Boy, stop playing, grab my ass ♪
♪ Why you actin' like you shy ♪
♪ Shut it, save it, keep it, pushin' ♪
♪ Why you beating 'round the bush ♪
♪ And knowing you want all this woman ♪
♪ Never knock it 'til you try ♪
♪ All of them bitches
hating I have you with me ♪
♪ All of my niggas saying
you mad committed ♪
♪ Realer than anybody
you had, and pretty ♪
♪ All of that body-ody,
the ass and titties ♪
♪ Day to night to morning,
keep with me in the moment ♪
♪ I'd let you had I known
it, why don't you say so ♪
♪ Didn't even notice, no
punches left to roll with ♪
♪ You got to keep me focused,
you want it, say so ♪
♪ Day to night to morning,
keep with me in the moment ♪
♪ I'd let you had I known
it, why don't you say so ♪
♪ Didn't even notice, no
punches left to roll with ♪
♪ You got to keep me focused,
you want it, say so ♪
(light upbeat music continues)
♪ Day to night to morning,
keep with me in the moment ♪
♪ I'd let you had I known
it, why don't you say so ♪
♪ Didn't even notice, no
punches left to roll with ♪
♪ You got to keep me focused,
you want it, say so ♪
(light music)